[theme music playing]
[laughs]
[Salonga] We must study this
more thoroughly
before we get foreign intelligence
involved in Red Dragon's case.
[Lily] I have a spy in
Red Dragon's organization.
We can keep track of their every move.
[Mercedes] Unless I'm certain
of your loyalty, Diego,
I cannot just trust you blindly.
[Lily] I'm worried that
Mercedes has Diego's phone.
[Damian] Maybe I can help.
I used to be in a gang
with Red Dragon's former men.
[Mercedes] We can't do anything to Diego
without any solid proof.
[Helena] And while I'm away,
I am entrusting my position
to my baby girl.
My baby dragon, Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
You are not my queen,
and you will never be.
I'd rather die than kneel before you.
[Emilia] Vanessa, you know
what to do with her.
[Lily] Emilia is born
to lead your faction,
but you are made to rule.
You deserve better,
and you'll get that in my group.
I'd much rather be alone
than become your little pet.
Emilia and Red Dragon's group
are planning a huge meeting.
It could be the perfect chance
to arrest them.
[Julio] The lion is not gonna sleep
until he puts this pesky flock of sheep
down the drain.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Little Red Riding Hood!
Where do you think you're going?
And since when did I have to
ask for your permission, Papa?
I'm asking you properly.
Where are you going?
Spare me, Papa, okay?
You're ruining my good mood.
Wherever it is, you're not going.
No, Papa! I know this already.
The lion is envious of the lioness
because you know that after that meeting,
I'll become more powerful than you,
and you don't want that. I know that.
Enough with your delusions, Emilia.
When I say you can't go,
you can't go.
And you will thank me for this later on,
because believe it or not,
I'm doing all this for you.
That's it! I'm done
being your loyal follower.
I'm done being your daughter.
I won't follow your orders anymore.
That's it. So, goodbye.
[gunshots]
[screams]
[Emilia gasps]
[hyperventilates]
[groans]
[groaning]
[shrieks]
[ominous music]
And what was that for, Papa?
Are you trying to kill me?!
Of course not!
I just wanted to get your attention.
I missed, see?
Can you please tell me what's going on?
[tense music playing]
That's it. I'm leaving.
[Emilia yelps]
Enough, Papa! You're scaring me!
She's so stubborn!
Magbanua.
Call your men,
and tell them that
my stubborn little daughter
is on her way there.
I don't know what I'm going
to do with that woman.
[Arnaldo crying]
[panting]
[shouts]
[shrieks]
[ominous music playing]
[groans]
[groaning]
-[ominous music intensifies]
-[Arnaldo hyperventilates]
[Ivy] Mr. Mayor, my name is Ivy.
Ivy Aguas.
[Arnaldo] You really are
something else, Miss Aguas.
[Ivy] I'm sure of my feelings for you.
Arnaldo, I'm not playing you.
I love you.
I love you, Arnaldo.
[Arnaldo] Ivy Aguas, I love you.
-Will you marry me?
-Yes, Arnaldo.
[Nimfa] She's the one feeding
information to Diego's camp.
-That's not true!
-She's Diego's spy!
That's not true!
Mayor, you need to know that Ivy is--
-That's not true!
-[gunshot]
[Arthur] I've got Ivy Aguas.
[Arnaldo] Well, I have you!
I can easily kill you
and make it look
like you committed suicide,
just like what I did to Carlotta.
-You monster!
-I didn't mean to!
-But you love me!
I don't love you!
[Ivy] Mom.
[Camia] Lily, dear.
[Arnaldo] Tell me.
You're Lily Cruz, right?
Answer me!
[Lily] Yes! I am!
I am Lily Cruz!
-No!
-[gunshot]
[ethereal music playing]
[Arnaldo] Ivy Aguas.
You were my happiness.
But you also caused my downfall.
[tense music playing]
You killed the old Arnaldo.
But now that my memory is back,
I'll make you pay.
[tense music intensifies]
Yeah. She's already there.
Mercedes, who invited you?
Didn't Madam Baby Dragon
already kick you out?
I wasn't kicked out.
I simply went on vacation.
Why, were you two invited?
Of course.
[Mercedes] Well, not anymore.
[tense music playing]
Yes, I'm back.
A bunch of bruises won't keep me
from being at this event.
Just make sure you're loyal to Emilia.
Otherwise,
you'll get something worse than that.
[tense music continues]
[Emilia] Come on. Let's move!
I'm in a hurry! Move it!
Drive!
[tense music swelling]
Mr. Ramon Lim of the North.
Welcome, sir.
Mr. Silverio Victoria of the East.
Welcome.
Mr. Carlos Isidro of the West. Welcome.
Mr. Oscar Evangelista
of the South. Welcome.
[tense music intensifies]
-Cheers!
-[glasses clinking]
-[laughter, chatter in the background]
[man] Cheers! Cheers, everyone.
[Mercedes] Thank you for gracing
this occasion.
And as a token of our appreciation,
Red Dragon has prepared something
to delight your senses.
-Wow.
-Yes.
-Cheers! Cheers!
-[glasses clinking]
-Yeah!
[man] I like it.
I like it, I like it, I like it!
[man] Very good! I like it!
-Hello.
-How are you?
Very nice!
Beautiful! Beautiful!
[tense music playing]
[Magbanua] Governor.
Our men have been notified that
your daughter is on the way.
That's good.
Make sure nothing happens to my daughter.
Yes, sir.
[Magbanua] Let's go.
[exhales]
[man] Beautiful!
Very nice!
Governor.
Yes, that's the one.
-I'll take my leave, sir.
-Okay, thank you.
[men laughing]
-Cheers!
Cheers!
[glasses clinking]
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat music playing]
Yes.
[tense music playing]
[phone buzzing]
Lily, it's me, Diego.
Diego, we're here.
Don't come in yet.
Something doesn't feel right.
We're already here, Diego.
If your suspicions are correct…
then we shouldn't waste any more time!
Are they all there?
Emilia's still not here.
Why isn't she there yet?
[suspenseful music swelling]
[Julio] It's been a while.
[classical music playing]
-[man] Waiter.
-Sweet.
This must be what they call
the nectar of the gods from Mount Olympus.
Cheers.
[music continues]
[gunshots]
[Emilia screams]
What was that? Go check it out!
[gunshots]
[classical music swells]
-[gunshots]
-[classical music playing]
[gunfire continue]
Diego?
-Let's go.
-Move! Move!
[gunshots]
[classical music continues]
[rapid gunfire]
[music continues]
[gunfire continues over classical music]
[classical music fades]
So, this…
is what victory tastes like.
[Julio] Soft.
Mellow.
Full-bodied and warm.
I can't go wrong.
Cheers to life.
My life.
[tense music intensifies]
-[gunshots]
-[Emilia screams]
[groans]
[gunshots]
-[gunfire continues]
-[tense music intensifies]
-[gunshot]
-[yelps]
[Jaguar] Let's go, Emilia!
Lily, let's go!
What are you talking about?!
Can't you see?!
This is a massacre, Agent Salonga!
My men are already in position!
It's important for us
to keep you safe! Let's go!
If the Big Four die, who will
testify against Red Dragon?!
[gunshots]
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
Mercedes.
[gunshots]
Get up! Come on!
Let's go.
-Come with me.
-I won't go with you.
If you don't come with me,
you'll die here!
[action music playing]
[suspenseful music swelling]
[knocking on door]
Come in!
Ma'am, something bad happened
to Boss Oscar.
What do you mean?
Boss Oscar died along with the
other members of the Big Four!
What? My Oscar is dead?
Yes, ma'am!
That's why we need to hide and lie low.
They might come for us next.
This can't be.
No.
We will not hide.
I'll make sure that his business
continues to thrive.
He put this up.
And I know that he wants me to continue.
All operations will continue.
Now, tell everyone…
that I will be taking over the business.
Do you have a problem with that?
Do you?
I think you're forgetting
that Oscar ordered you
to do everything I say.
Just so you know,
I hold all the transaction
records of this business.
Hmm?
Yes, ma'am. We're aware of that.
Good.
Now, go and tell everyone who's boss.
While I'll be grieving…
for my Oscar.
[cries]
Go! Just go and leave me!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Daddy.
[exhales]
That was so fast, Daddy.
[laughs]
That's it?
Well, Natalie…
I guess I need to propose a toast
to me.
Cheers, Natalie.
[laughs]
Four syndicate bosses,
known as The Big Four,
were recently massacred.
They were identified as Oscar
Evangelista, Carlos Isidro,
Silverio Victoria, and Ramon Lim.
They were known to be associates
of the most powerful crime lord
in the country, known as Red Dragon,
who was recently identified
as Helena Montoya.
Authorities have been unable
to locate her until now.
So, where is Red Dragon?
Who is behind the massacre of her allies?
[laughs]
[reporter] Stay tuned for more updates.
This is Willie Gabon, reporting.
-[shouts]
-[phone clatters]
-[shouting]
-[thumping]
[Julio] Who could the mastermind be?
[laughs]
[claps]
[sighs contently]
Ouch! Hey, be careful! It hurts!
I'm sorry. But I'm done anyway.
Wait.
How did you know
that my life was in danger?
Didn't I tell you that…
I'd always keep an eye on you?
Wait, did you install a
CCTV camera in my house?
Or did you ask someone to spy on me?
No.
I've already told you that
I will watch your every move…
and that I'll protect you.
So, can you please stop
asking so many questions?
Hmm.
Wait. Jaguar, do you have any idea
who could be behind the bloodbath earlier?
I'll find out eventually.
You know, I have a feeling it's Mercedes.
Because Mercedes knew I was
getting along with the Big Four.
And she wants to take my position, right?
So, she's the mastermind!
I can bet my life on that.
That's impossible.
You mentioned that she was
at the meeting earlier.
She couldn't have been the mastermind.
You have a point.
Um, I think it's Lily Cruz.
It's Lily Cruz.
I can bet my life on it
for the second time.
She's the mastermind.
She'd never do that, Emilia.
She's incapable of killing people.
Oh, please, Jaguar!
Can you please stop antagonizing me?
And just support me, okay?
Emilia, I'm merely stating facts.
Shush. Just support me, okay?
[ominous music playing]
Arnaldo?
What happened to you? Are you okay?!
Come on, I'll take you to the hospital.
No.
I'm fine.
Thank you for your concern.
Are you sure?
Bless you.
Okay. I'll leave now.
I just came back for these books.
Take care.
[ominous music intensifies]
-Good morning, friend.
-"Friend"?!
-You're a murderer!
-Wait! Hold on!
[Arnaldo] You seem to know who I am.
-You're Arnaldo Ardiente.
-Good for you.
I don't even know who I am.
-Peace be with you.
-Just drop the act, will you?!
-Jepoy, stop it.
-Anna!
Don't defend that bastard!
He'll kill you!
But he wasn't fighting back, right?
Have you ever thought
of returning to your family?
I know why you're asking me this.
You're making sure I've really changed.
What are you hiding from me?
Why don't you just forget
about everything, Arnaldo?!
This is your chance to start over.
Anna.
Where are you going?
None of your business.
You're still rude to me
after I saved your life?
I didn't ask you to do that,
so I don't owe you anything.
But, you know what?
Just so we can settle this,
how much do you want?
I'll pay you.
[tense music]
You think I need your dirty money?
You can keep it, Mercedes.
[sighs]
But I want you to know I can
help you take Red Dragon down.
[scoffs]
Leave me out of your crazy schemes.
I'm not crazy.
You only got shot on the shoulder, right?
Then why do you sound
like you have brain damage?
For your information,
Red Dragon wants you dead.
She wants all of you dead.
-That's not true!
-It is.
Don't be stupid, Mercedes.
In times like these,
you can't afford to be stupid.
And in case you didn't know,
she had the Big Four killed
so she could hold on to all the power.
If she could do that to her partners,
what more to a mere lackey like you?
No.
I trust Red Dragon.
And no matter what you say,
I will never side with you.
I would rather die than turn
my back on Red Dragon--
You're siding with the devil!
I'd rather do that than work with you.
Remember, Mercedes.
You need me more than I need you.
If you've made up your mind, then fine.
I just hope you don't regret
the stupid choice you made.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[tense music swelling]
[birds chirping]
Emilia!
Emilia, come here.
Join me for breakfast.
-Good morning, Papa.
-Good morning. Good morning.
Come on.
Um…
What seems to be wrong with your arm?
-Nothing's wrong, Papa.
-Oh, nothing? Really?
-What if I do this?
-[Emilia screams]
-Papa!
-See?
You flinched even before I hit you.
That just proves my point.
You went to the meeting, didn't you?
I have an obligation
to Mama's organization.
[Julio sighs]
This is what happens
when you don't listen to me.
I told you to just stay home
and not go there.
But you were so stubborn.
See what happened?
Were you behind the attack, Papa?
Oh, come on, Emilia.
Are you seriously accusing me of
doing something wrong or evil?
-Don't be silly.
-Oh, come on, Papa.
You wanted me to stay home.
How did you know what would happen?
I wasn't insisting on anything.
Look.
This is what happens
to criminal organizations
when a power struggle occurs.
In the end, the members
go against each other,
to the point where they end up
killing one another.
You see, I've seen this over and over
and over and over again.
That's why there's nothing
special about me
knowing or sensing
something bad would happen.
Pure and simple common sense.
And that's your problem.
You always lead with your heart,
and not with your head.
Good grief, Emilia.
You should use your head
every now and then.
I mean, you have common sense.
You just choose not to use it.
[tense music playing]
Have some water.
Did you hear about what happened
to the Big Four?
Big Four?
I called Lily up.
She says she's all right.
But we need to be on high alert.
They might end up needing our help.
I'm glad you're talking to me again.
I'm just being careful, Anna.
I don't want to upset you again.
[Jepoy's phone ringing]
[line ringing]
[quietly] I want you.
[Jepoy's phone rings]
Hey, lover boy.
[Natalie] So…
I've been a bad girl.
Are you going to punish me?
Hmm?
[tense music playing]
That was weird.
-What are you doing?
-Miss Mercedes.
We thought you were dead.
Who told you that?
Ma'am Emilia did.
She also told us to clean
because she was about to arrive.
You are high-level assassins,
not that woman's maids!
-[door opens]
-[Emilia clears throat]
Wow!
Look who's back!
Back from the dead…
with that look.
Aww.
Don't tell me you're indestructible too?
You don't have any originality.
[tense music playing]
[Emilia grunts]
I've been wanting to do this
for a long time.
But I kept my cool because of Red Dragon.
But now, I've had enough of your attitude.
[Emilia groaning]
[Mercedes grunts, pants]
You silly witch!
You crumpled my expensive silk top!
What's with that look?
-Hey!
-Ask your girlfriend.
What are you talking about?
[phone clatters]
Huh?
Is this how you really see me?
Do you really think I'm this low, Anna?
Yes!
Because I can't give you what you want.
I can't satisfy your desires!
You're right! I do have needs!
But I'm willing to wait
for the day you'll be ready.
Because I love you, Anna.
I love you so much.
You're the only one for me!
There's no one else. Just you.
[Mercedes and Emilia grunt]
Restrain that skinny twig!
[tense music]
I knew it, Mercedes.
From the moment I first saw you,
I knew you wanted to steal my crown!
I don't care about you
and your mother's crown!
All I care about is our survival!
Survival? With that look? Come on!
Stop acting like you're a superhero!
You are so clueless!
The Big Four's men will blame us
for what happened!
They'll get back at us!
You just put everyone's lives at risk!
That's just your opinion!
That is a fact!
And I am the only one who can stop them.
That's why I am taking over
as leader of this group.
[laughs]
Leader?
Leader of this group?
Did I just hear you say that, huh?
That you're the leader of this group?
And how can that be,
when I am the queen
and leader of this group?
Idiot!
Now, I am giving you
five seconds to side with me.
[Emilia] Five!
[Mercedes] Don't waste your
breath counting.
Four!
Because they know who to trust.
Three!
Just accept that you're
completely powerless!
-Two!
-Just like--
[woman] One.
[suspenseful music]
Red Dragon?
Mama!
I'm sorry, Mercedes.
I seem to have cut you off.
Were you saying something?
-[Emilia giggles]
-Hello, darling.
[Emilia chuckles]
Never mind.
Time is of the essence here,
and every second counts.
Get everyone here because
I already know who betrayed me.
Mercedes!
Yes, Madam.
Bye!
Let's play a little game.
Who do you suspect
was behind the massacre?
Right now, all we have
are persons of interest.
I'm here because we've received intel
confirming Red Dragon's location.
Did you find her?
Um…
Based on our intel, she's in Macau.
But she's always on the move,
so we really couldn't pinpoint
her exact location.
Agent Salonga, four of
Red Dragon's leaders got killed.
Do you think she would just
let her organization crumble?
-What do you mean?
-It's simple.
Red Dragon's not in Macau.
She's here in the Philippines
to tend to her organization.
It's that simple.
You can't find her in Macau,
because she's here in the Philippines.
[phone rings]
Mercedes?
Drop whatever you're doing,
and come here.
Why?
You'll know when you get here.
[tense music swelling]
LILY, I'M ON MY WAY.
WAIT FOR ME.
[mellow music playing]
I LOVE ANNA.
He really loves me.
Why do you have my phone?
Give me that!
You'll think the worst of me again.
Lily.
Diego.
Red Dragon is back.
So that's why Mercedes
wants all of us there.
Please, don't go back there.
Please, Diego.
Lily, there's no turning back now.
We're so close to taking Red Dragon down.
Then you better take this.
Keep this with you at all times.
What's this?
A tracking device.
So we always know where you are.
[Diego] This could be our last chance
to take Red Dragon down.
She has a huge transaction coming up.
We have to catch her.
[Lily] Just tell me the time,
date, and place,
so we can finally
put a muzzle over her mouth.
[Helena] All of you have
a reason to betray me.
[Emilia] Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Moe, moe!
[gunshot]
[Julio] You truly are back.
I love this!
My grandson is back!
[Arnaldo] Cheers.
[theme music playing]